１人か…　感心だな。 どこで死ぬ？
Next is the continuation of
our report on the UMAs, or Unidentified Mysterious Animals,
that have recently been sighted.
好きな所で殺してやるよ。 ひとに迷惑が　かからない 荒野がいいな。
The difference between this and our previous
report is the increasing number of victims, and the amount of evidence supporting
the existence of these creatures.
お前の断末魔は　うるさそうだ。
In any case, many of the witnesses are
active members of the police force.
殺した者達のことを 覚えているか？
A x Lawless x Home
少しはな。 まぁ　印象に残った相手なら 忘れねえぜ。
They're known as Chimera Ants. I know.
つまるところ　復讐か。
They became that way after mixing with humans.
誰の弔い合戦だ？ クルタ族。 ん？　知らねえな。
Working backwards from the dates and
locations of sightings and police reports, they probably originated in the Balsa Islands.
緋の眼を持つ ルクソ地方の少数民族だ。
Lots of strange nations are in that area. You shouldn't be talking about
how strange other people are.
５年ほど前　お前達に襲われた。
But they were once ants...
「ヒノメ」？　何だそりゃ お宝の名前だってか。
So they should just stay close to their nest. Why come all the way out here?
悪いが記憶にねえな。
No idea.
５年前なら 俺も参加してるはずなんだが…。
Maybe they were just wandering, or perhaps
they were drawn to the smell of garbage. It can't be a coincidence.
およそ　かかわりのない人間を 殺す時
Both NGL and East Gorteau are nations
お前は…　お前達は
that share no information with the outside world.
一体　何を考え 何を感じているんだ？
Just like this place.
別に　何も。
That makes it easier for them to invade.
死で償え！
The place hasn't changed...
殺しはな！
What's the situation?
俺の一番の喜びってやつを 教えてやろうか？ おめぇみてぇな　リベンジ野郎を
Between the victims and martyrs,
we're seeing over three hundred dead.
返り討ちにすることだ！
Bombs have no effect, so we can't fight back.
この鎖がヤベェ
The Ants did this? Looks dead to me.
どんな手品を使ったか 分からねえが
What's the problem?
通常じゃ　考えられねえほどの 「念」が　あれに込められてやがる
Some are alive and working with the Ants.
と　来れば…
And all of them look like monsters.
先手必勝！
The council's debate is whether
to declare them dead based on whether or not there's a way to
restore them to their original forms.
手応え　あり！
They can't avenge them because
なお　攻撃して来る気力が あるとはなぁ
Nothing's changed.
だが　左腕は イカレちまったはずだ
They always lose sight of what's important. We're going to do things our way.
なっ　無傷？　バカな…
If anyone interferes, we'll take them down. Don't worry.
鎖に　あれだけの「念」を 込めることができるのは 物体を操る　操作系か オーラを物体化する　具現化系
Before the day is out, we'll exterminate this so-called Queen.
奴は　恐らく前者
I am the Queen.
しかし　俺の拳を 生身で防御できるのは
I repeat.
強化系ぐらいなはず
Surrender.
奴は　一体… 今のパンチ。 ん？ まさか　全力か？
Those who resist will be executed. The chosen will live in paradise for eternity!
クッ…！
Our mother's greatest flaw
クックック…。
was that she could only produce soldiers
面白くもねえ冗談だな。
through the archaic and inefficient laying of eggs.
安心しろ　２割程度だ。
Her sole achievement
じゃあ　今度は 半分程度の力で行くぜ！
was giving birth to me. Stop...
おら！
Kill me! Kill me!
クッ…。
Plenty of spirit...
おら！
Chosen one, welcome to paradise.
クソ…　ちょこまかと 動き回りやがって。 だがな…。
Swear eternal fealty to the Queen.
「今の隙に　鎖で 俺を捕らえなかったことを 後悔するぜ」か？
I am the Queen.
ん？ くだらん負け惜しみはやめて 全力で来い。
With my Queen Shot, I shall control the world.
時間の無駄だ。
Let's go through the front door.
やってやるぜ。
No objection here...
すさまじいほどのオーラだ。
No one's around. Are they inviting us in?
目くらまし？
I'll take this way. We're splitting up?
気配が消えた…
Of course... It's a race to see
who'll kill the Queen.
これは　「隠」！
I imagine you'd prefer to hide
your abilities from us.
今度こそ砕いたぜ。
Start!
本気を出した 俺の「ビッグバンインパクト」を
They've scattered.
生身で止められる奴なんぞ いねえ！ だが　褒めておくよ おめぇの　あの反応の速さ。
From their footsteps, I can sense
that these intruders are special.
恐らく　土煙の微妙な変化を 目の端で捉えたな。
They are accustomed to living in the wild. Are they strong?
こちらこそ褒めておこう まさか　「隠」を使えるとはな。
Yes. Then go and greet them.
地面をたたき　土煙を上げたのは 体だけでなく　気配をも絶って 攻撃する作戦だったわけだな。
But then, no one will be here to guard you. If you're worried about me, capture the enemy and hurry back.
だが
I have faith in you, Pike.
「隠」を使えるのは　私も同じ。 ん？
Y-You are too kind...
まさか！
I will serve you with my life!
見えたか？
Off I go!
「凝」も使えるようだな。
Now, then...
この鎖は　念能力で オーラを具現化したもの。
You're heading out? My mother's greatest misfortune
従って 「隠」で見えなくすることも可能。 お前が普段も 鎖を具現化してたのは
was that she never experienced
the joy of combat.
敵は　見える鎖にだけ 注意を払うだろう。
You're no fun...
まさに今　それが証明された。
Let me hold you.
お前が　つまらん 強がりを言いかけた時
I'll send you to heaven.
こいつ　強化系と具現化系の 両方の能力を 最大限まで極めてやがるのか？
Bonolenov descended from a small tribe
that industrialization had driven out of
あり得ねえぞ！
its ancestral lands, the Gyudondond.
本来　念能力者が１００％まで 極めることが可能なのは 生まれつきの 系統能力だけのはず
When Gyudondond males reach the age of three, needles are used to puncture holes in their body.
「解せない」という面持ちだな。 黄泉の手向けに教えてやろう。
Depending on the holes' size and shape, and the movements the Gyudondond
make, they can produce sound.
あっ…！
Before fighting rival tribes or wild animals, they would play a battle song using
their own bodies as instruments.
その目…　思い出したぜ。
They are known as the Bapu, dancing warriors. They believe the more beautiful
コソコソ奥地で暮らしてた奴ら。
the sound produced, the stronger
the spirit that descends.
団長が　いたく気に入ってたぜ。 あいつら　強かったな。
The most skilled Bapu are treated as gods, and hold more influence than the elders.
フフフ…　燃えて来たぜ！
Transform this melody into strength to fight! Battle Cantabile...
てめぇの恨みと　俺の怪力
Prologue!
外道め お前の頭の中は　それだけか。 お前ごときに　この鎖は切れん！
The blood of my tribe, the most beautiful in battle,
flows through my veins.
うお!!
I swear on the names of the spirits and my tribe that you will not best me.
ハァ　ハァ…。
Was that attack supposed
to hold your tribe's pride?
なぜだ　どうして…！
If so...
緋の眼が発現した時のみ 私は特質系に変わる。
You must not feel much pride.
何だと？
Don't bother recanting those words.
特質系となった私は
They are but a beast's ramblings.
どの系統の能力も １００％引き出せる。
They cannot affect me!
これが今の私の力 「エンペラータイム」！
In a one-on-one fight, my opponent's
strength doesn't matter.
) )
Those are sharp...
((具現化系と聞いた時 最初に頭に浮かんだものだ)) )
I'll need to slip in between them and insert the antenna into the joint
exposed when he moves the arm.
((地獄に　つないでおかねば ならないような連中が
Chance of succeeding unscathed... Twenty percent!
)
Okay, it worked...
((てめぇ！　ちょっと待て！ 一応　俺は師匠だぞ！)) )
Ow. Guess escaping unharmed wasn't possible.
)
Huh?
((ただの鎖を物質化しても 意味ねえんだぞ！))
Why didn't it work?
((かといって 絶対に　ちぎれない鎖なんて
I put the antenna in...
具現化　不可能だ！))
You must be a Manipulator.
((無視ね…　ったく 言い出したら聞きやしねえ))
I can tell because, once you placed
that antenna in Pell, you relaxed. That must be the condition
for activating your power.
((絶対に　ちぎれない鎖は 無理だが
You let your guard down
when you thought it worked.
限りなく　それに近くすることは できるぜ？))
Its name is Pell?
)
You must also be a Manipulator.
((まったく！ 都合のいい耳だこと)) ) )
If my power doesn't activate after
the condition has been met, that means my target is already being
manipulated by another Nen user.
) )
That, and he has a remote controller.
((「制約」 すなわち　ルールを決めて
Oh, you knew?
それを心に誓うんだ))
Yes, it's first come, first served for Manipulators.
((順守すると そのルールが厳しいほど 使う技は 爆発的な威力を発揮する))
Once I take you to the Queen, my job is done.
((普段の念能力の補強が 足し算なら
No good... I can't break free.
条件つきの「念」の奥義は 掛け算だ))
Guess there's no choice.
)
I'd rather not have to use this...
((その鎖にルールを作れ お前の覚悟で守れる範囲のな))
Your punch stings about as
much as a mosquito bite.
((ただし　言っておくが これは安定とは正反対の大技 もろ刃の剣だ))
What's next? You gonna kick me? Pull out a weapon? As a gift to you on your way to the afterlife,
I'll grant you one more attack.
((もし　誓いを破れば　反動で
For an ant, you know some big words.
念能力を失う危険があることを 忘れるな))
Then I'll take you up on that...
((私の目的は 仲間の緋の眼を捜し出し
You're sure? Really?
「クモ」を捕らえること))
Fifteen should do it. Fifteen?
((「クモ」を… 「幻影旅団」を捕らえたら 決して逃さない鎖が欲しい))
Four, five, six...
((目標以外に 使用しないってルールか)) )
Eleven, twelve, thirteen, fourteen...
((早まるな　奴ら以外に その鎖を使わないというのは
Fifteen!
ただの前提条件だ))
Huh?
)
I get a free attack, right?
((おい　クラピカ… 緋の眼になったら
Every time I wind my arm, my punch gets stronger.
オーラの絶対量が かなり増えてねえか？))
Ripper Cyclotron!
特質系？
Oh, half of that would have been enough.
全ての系統の力を １００％引き出せる…　だと？
I never seem to know how much power to use. Now, then...
その通り。
Which way to go?
折れた腕も　自己治癒力の強化で 完治。
What's going to happen to me?
完全に　バキバキに ぶち折った骨が
You'll become a slave. You'll work for the Queen until you die.
あっという間に…
Not too different from your current life.
最初の相手に　お前を選んだのには いくつかの理由がある。
That's true, in a sense.
お前が マフィアと「陰獣」との戦闘時
I'd just be taking orders from a different person.
お前の仲間は　全く 加勢する様子を見せなかった。
But I'd rather die than listen
to someone I don't even like. Strong words.
これは お前が単独で戦うことを好み
Well, at this point, all you
can move is your mouth.
かつ　戦闘に関して 多大な信頼を得ている証拠。
I can move both hands and my left leg. That's nice.
１対１の戦いは　私も望むところ。
Anyway, ready for me to take control? I can't let you die.
その点で　お前は好都合だった。 自らの防御力
Once I put this in you... When I fight, I always carry two antennae. For just this kind of situation.
攻撃力に絶対的な自信を持つ 強化系能力者
First come, first served.
これは　私が最初に 戦っておかねばならない
He stuck it in himself!
必須条件の相手。
Autopilot on.
なぜなら　その結果によって 私の「チェーンジェイル」が お前ら「旅団」全員に 通用するのかどうかが
S-So much aura...
分かるからだ。
Enemy identified.
「チェーンジェイル」は 捕らえた「旅団」を
Eliminating now.
強制的に「絶」にする。
Go, Pell!
その上で肉体の自由を奪う。
Aim for his leg! Remove the antenna!
うぅ…！ 「絶」は　オーラが全く出ない状態。
Mission complete. Autopilot disengaging.
つまり この鎖に捕らえられた者は
Powering off.
肉体の力のみで 鎖を断ち切らねばならない。 クソ！
Ow...
「旅団」の中で最も腕力のある お前が鎖を切れなければ
I already feel it... I'll be down with muscle aches
for two or three days.
他の団員にも 「チェーンジェイル」は切れない道理。
That's why I hate using this!
強制的な「絶」 確かに　これはヤベェ…
It makes me stronger, but there's a hefty price.
オーラは 念能力のエネルギー源 それが封じられたら 能力そのものを出せなくなる
And I remember nothing that happened, so I don't feel like I've accomplished anything.
念能力を封じる能力… こいつ　考えてやがる グッ！
You have considerable power for a lady. Where was she hiding that vacuum cleaner?
生身のお前と 強化した私の拳とでは
Where's the Queen? Rejoice. She stands before you now.
やや私の攻撃力のほうが 勝っているようだ。
That's a lame joke.
これは貴重な情報だな。 クッ。 捕らえてしまいさえすれば
Huh? A joke? You have no manners, brat.
This warrants a hefty punishment.
「旅団」全員を 素手で倒せることが分かった。
They are but a beast's ramblings. Then I'll take you up on that.
お前が知っていること 全て話してもらおう。 うぅ…。
When I fight, I always carry two antennae.
うぉ…！
It sounds like Feitan found the Queen...
仲間の居場所は？
How do I kill her first?
殺せ。
What's this? A child?
他に　どんな能力者が？
Then I'll come to you.
うぅ…！　ぐはっ！
What's that? Confetti.
手に残る感触　耳障りな音 血の臭い！
That didn't even tickle.
全てが神経に障る。 なぜ　貴様は何も考えず
Surrounding me with more paper?
何も感じずに こんなまねが　できるんだ！ 答えろ！
You're wasting your time! Look.
殺せ。
What? You think that means something?
うっ！
You really are a stupid kid!
最後のチャンスだ。
Impossible...
貴様の心臓に 戒めの楔を刺し込んだ。 私が定めた法を破れば 即座に鎖が発動し
This rope is made of steel! My fan is made of paper.
定められた法とは 私の質問に偽りなく答えること。 それさえ守れば しばらく生かしておいてもいい。
Meandering Dance.
フフフ…。
Look.
くたばれ　バカが。
Your right arm is next.
ぐはっ！
An umbrella?
うっ…　ハァ…。
A hidden blade?
少し…　長く変わり過ぎたか
You like hiding things on you, little boy? As do you.
[TEL]
When an opponent wears baggy clothing, it's safe to assume they're hiding something.
そうか　分かった。
What's wrong? Are you not going to continue your attack?
特殊な能力を付加する 能力者が多く
Battle Cantabile...
その能力次第では ウボォーの力が通じない場合がある。 操作系は　ウボォー本人が 操作される場合がヤバい。
Jupiter!
戻らぬウボォーギンに 危機感を募らせるシャルナーク
Crushed to death.
その意をくみ　団長　クロロも 鎖使いの抹殺へ 動こうとしていた
An appropriate death for a bug.